Our crowd goes away the second we take a break...
Sensei, do you have any tips
for how to keep it going?
You have to take care of yourself,
and that means taking breaks.
We're gonna take five!
The crowd leaves because their time is limited,
and they want pictures of other cosplayers.
You have to convince them you're worth waiting for.
Sorry, we'll be ready again in a second!
It's okay!
I'll wait as long as
I need to get a good pic of you.
Take your time!
This is one of the troubles
with larger cosplay groups.
Miss Liliel's strength is her infinite number of poses,
but her groupmates can't match that.
Here, with her group,
she can't use any of her strengths
to their collective advantage.
The World We Create with Our Friends
Was coming as a full group a bad idea?
No, we wouldn't get this much
attention without the full group.
There's gotta be a way we can make this work!
Ririsa-chan.
Just tell me what pose to do.
That's the only way we'll get more people!
I can, but Mikari-chan and Aria-chan
won't be able to keep up...
Yeah, I wouldn't know what scene
or pose you're even talking about.
Ririsa and Nono-pi would be so much better
off without me holding them back...
Wait, am I the one ruining this for them?
It's okay! I'll try harder!
This was all my idea, after all!
Okay, then what should I do?
Love the positivity,
but how are you gonna 'try harder'?
Wait, hold on.
Ririsa-chan, did you drink any water yet?
Um, well...
Cosplay Perfectionist
Liliel wouldn't drink regular bottled water...
What?!
And I don't want to mess up my makeup,
so I used a lot of powder to stop me from sweating.
Come on, Ririsa-chan!
I know, but I've been the
perfect Liliel all day today!
I can't stop now!
There's perfectionism and then
there's being ridiculous!
Hydrate, now!
I know this is overkill,
but this is the way I have to cosplay.
Still...
Guys!
I like Ririsa's take on cosplay.
We should let her do whatever she thinks is right.
Aria-chan...
That's why...
I'm not gonna drink water, either.
I want to try doing this your way, too.
B-but, that's crazy!
My idea of perfection is seriously ridiculous.
I couldn't make someone else,
let alone one of my friends,
try to match me.
You're kinda just doing your own thing, then...
Hey, guys!
Senpai, you've gotta talk to Ririsa...
I heard the whole thing.
I already came with a plan for
Ririsa's dedication to perfection.
Liliel's Pure Mythril Bento Box Set
So I brought the mythril bento box set
Liliel used in the manga!
It's got a water bottle!
Huh?!
Liliel can drink out of that, yeah?
But Senpai, it's an unopened box!
And it's super rare...
Yup. They only ever made five sets!
What?!
S-so that's one of five?
It's gotta be worth something!
A-are you sure about this?
Any real otaku would be happy to
have Liliel use his rare treasure.
Senpai...
That was suave enough to
make me forget how weird he is.
Hey, look at that Liliel.
She's drinking from the mythril bottle.
Damn... And she's staying completely in character!
The real Liliel is here with us...
Listen up, Autobots.
I've got an idea.
That's a death flag, Optimus.
We're ready for photos!
They're all looking in the same direction!
If we can't sync our poses,
then we can at least get
them looking the same way!
I'll be their target.
Look right at me!
They're looking my way!
Their crowd's getting big again.
Good for them! I love having competition.
Same, but it's really starting to get hot...
Yeah. Let's rest a little longer.
Okumura!
I know things are going well,
but you need to make
sure they're taking water breaks!
G-got it.
Liliel! Break time!
If we can't do more poses,
then I have to make sure
every tiny detail is perfect.
Damn...
Yeah, that Liliel is incredible.
She's in a class of her own.
Can we post pics of them?
Yeah, they said that's cool.
These are gonna turn out great...
This is just Day One. I've gotta work harder.
At the very least,
I have to make sure my cosplay is perfect...
Huh?
Nonopi! You okay?
Y-yeah.
Ririsa, break time!
Ririsa-chan, are you okay?!
S-sorry, I got light-headed...
Liliel?! What happened?!
Did she pass out? Did she hit her head?
No, I caught her.
Sensei...
She might have heatstroke.
Let's get her inside where it's cool.
Then we'll see how she's feeling
and visit the first aid station.
Can you walk? We have to get you inside.
Is she okay?
Anyone see a staffer?
Sensei, I've got her.
Could you help me lift her?
Don't push yourself!
We don't want you to pass out, too!
Nonoa-chan...
I will protect you with my life.
Nokiel...
It's the real Nokiel.
Dude!
It's just a little heat exhaustion.
You're feeling better and drinking water,
but you should go home and rest to be safe.
But...
No buts!
She's right, Ririsa-chan!
I know, but...
Ariel wouldn't let her friend
Liliel push herself too hard.
Okay.
Mita, you see Liliel yet?
I saw some of Mikarin,
but for some reason,
I haven't seen anything since this morning.
It's fine.
Cosplay Roundup
Real twin cosplayers aim for the Heavenly Seat.
Real twin cosplayers aim for the Heavenly Seat
Lemon and Lime draw biggest crowd of Day 1.
Lemon and Lime draw biggest crowd of Day 1
Nagomi's industry booth appearance
draws her biggest crowd yet.
Nagomi's industry booth appearance draws her biggest crowd yet
No Mayura-sama this year...
Are Lemon/Lime next up for Queen?
Day 1 is over, hottest temperatures
ever cause exhaustion, heatstroke...
The vibes are so off.
Okay, what do we do tomorrow?
We're going if Ririsa feels better, right?
Yeah, of course!
I'm so sorry about today. It's all my fault.
How is it your fault?
Literally anyone could've passed out in that heat.
No, I should've prepped better! I-I know it's my fault!
I'll do better tomorrow, promise!
I'll come up with something. You guys just relax!
If anyone should be relaxing, it's you!
Okay, but...
I-it's okay, Mikarin...
N-Nonoa-chan?!
Stop it, okay?
"I'll think of something."
"I'll do better."
"I couldn't force you."
"You guys relax."
Stop doing everything yourself!
You said you'd be my friend, right?
So let me help!
I get it, you're just being nice.
But, you're nice to everyone!
So what's the point of being friends,
if you're just gonna treat us like everyone else?!
You don't have to do this by yourself!
Tell us what you're thinking.
Tell us what you want to do!
I might not be able to do that,
and I might think it's a pain...
But I still want you to ask me!
If I don't want to do it, or if I can't do it, I'll tell you.
Don't make assumptions for me!
Not when I finally have the
courage to tell you how I feel!
The local train bound for Hiyoshi is approaching on Track 2.
I get it. You know how much easier
it is to do things by yourself.
Everything is easier when you don't have friends.
You don't have to worry about
anyone else other than yourself.
It's easy, but it kills you inside.
I felt so alone today.
We're supposed to be friends! Allies!
So let me sacrifice all I have to help win the battle!
Nonoa-chan...
I'm not about to like, sacrifice myself,
but I totally agree with her on everything else.
Sure, it was intense,
but isn't this the kind of
friendship you want right now?
Mikari-chan, Aria-chan...
Let's do this together, Ririsa!
I'm not made of free time,
so start telling me what to do, okay?
I don't wanna half-ass anything,
whether it's modeling or cosplaying.
Okay, next pose!
Dance practice, you think?
They're so cute.
This is the Lord Ashford pose!
Perfect, Nokiel!
Ariel, move your elbow a little to the left!
Miriella, your arm should be at a thirty-degree angle.
Don't go too hard just 'cause it's cooling off, okay?
That's all 50 of the big poses.
I want you guys to memorize them by tomorrow!
Are you crazy?!
Okay, I'll try.
Let's do this!
If you can remember all those,
I should at least try.
Ririsa remembers them because she loves the manga.
It might be easier for you guys
to memorize them with the story.
Like the poses from Volume 1
against their first enemy.
Then they get their new attack in Volume 2.
It's stronger and flashier,
hence the bigger pose.
That's the part during our watch party where
Ririsa spilled soda everywhere.
It's easier to remember when
you associate them with certain parts.
Even if you forget the names for stuff,
you'll still remember the big scenes.
If you do your poses in story order,
you should hit them all without faltering.
And then I won't have to tell
you which one to do next!
I'll put together the ordered
list while you guys practice.
Awesome, thank you so much!
Yes, that's it! Wow, everyone looks perfect!
Let's do it again from the top!
Isn't that your phone, Nonopi? It keeps going off.
Huh?! It's probably my Mom.
New follower:
It's follower notifications...
And they just keep coming!
What did I do?!
Oh, whoa...
When Liliel passed out,
Nokiel carried her off in her arms...
Just like a scene from the manga.
That picture went crazy viral!
I feel bad but omg my heart.
Uhhhh did they give permission for you to take this?
they're reporting what happened idiot
So that's why my notifications are popping off...
Is Liliel-chan OK?!
I wanted to get your pic!
Are you gonna be there tomorrow?
I'd love to get your group pic!
NONOA @ Summer Comiket Day 1
Thank you for all your comments.
Liliel-chan had heat exhaustion but she's okay now.
THANK GOD!!!!
It was literally hell on earth today with that heat.
Cosplayers were dropping like flies out there
NONOA @ Summer Comiket Day 1
If she's still OK tomorrow we'll all be there.
Damn, everyone says they're gonna come see us!
You've got a chance to redeem yourself,
all thanks to Nonoa.
Yeah.
Tomorrow, we're gonna bring out
the best cosplay ever, as a team!
Okay, circle up!
Man, this one again?
Liliel...
Explosion!
The temperature is supposed to
be way cooler than yesterday.
Senpai, I forgot my hat today!
Oh, I brought an extra!
Wow, thanks.
That's cute.
Okay, let's get changed.
Yeah!
Hey, guys?
You're sure it's okay for me to
tell you to do stuff today?
Oh.
Ugh, when are you gonna stop being 'nice' to us?
Do you need another lecture?
Just tell us what you want us to do, okay?!
Okay, so...
Today, I want to cosplay my way,
and I want you all to do it with me!
Lemon and Lime are Luc and Luka today!
We're gonna be Number One
for the second day in a row!
Wow, Lemon, I didn't know you
cared that much about the ranking.
Yeah, only because they gave us 2 and 3!
We're gonna earn that top spot this year...
Hey.
Yeah.
I-is this okay?
Everyone's looking at me like I'm the girl
who caused a bunch of drama yesterday.
You're being paranoid!
Everyone said they were excited to get our pics!
Please.
There's always a handful of people who will judge you,
even if you don't do anything.
You only notice them when
you're feeling bad about something.
Just forget they even exist.
Of course Mikarin knows how to deal with this.
She's been on TV.
Forget all that and just have fun!
Summer Comiket only comes once a year!
That's right!
I'm super excited to try to do this your way!
Liliel-chan!
We've been waiting for you!
I'm so glad you're okay!
You were so gallant yesterday, Nonoa-chan!
Mikarin!
Ariel, you're so adorable!
Let's begin.
We'll start with their group pose from Volume 1.
Once we've looked through the crowd,
we go to the next pose,
Volume 1's special attack.
This pose quality is incredible...
Their victory pose!
How'd they get this good in one day?!
Moving into Volume 2.
They've got more poses?!
The guys in front haven't even left yet!
There are tons of people behind us!
What's this huge crowd? It's not even noon yet!
Great to have competition, huh...
They're not gonna be able to see my target.
Are they doing okay?
That's not important anymore.
When you're cosplaying from the heart,
you don't need to worry about a thing.
It feels like I'm living in a dream.
A girl your age, playing dress-up?
When I'm alone,
it's easy to fall out of character
and remember my sad reality...
But, not right now.
Are you all right, Liliel-sama?
Worn out already, Liliel?
Rest, then! I got this!
Not when I have my friends by my side.
I'm counting on all three of you today,
Nokiel, Miriella, Ariel.
Our hearts are in this!
I found other people like me.
My dreams have become reality.
All my worries have disappeared.
I'm cosplaying with my friends.
And our only purpose is to express our overflowing love.
That love brings the world of the
manga to life right here, right now.
I couldn't be happier.
I dunno if we're taking number one today.
Hey, don't give up yet, Lime!
We're taking a five-minute break!
Ririsa...
I think I get why you cosplay this way.
For a split second,
it felt like I was really in
the world of my dad's manga.
Thank you, Ririsa.
I should be thanking you guys,
for teaching me how to be a good friend.
I know now that sacrificing yourself for
your friends isn't what friendship is about.
I also know how great it feels when
your friends give their all to help you.
My heart just feels so light and happy.
I'm having so much fun cosplaying in a group.
I'm so glad I got to come to Comiket with you guys.
Save your tears for later, Liliel!
She's right! We've still got this afternoon!
The fun's just getting started!
Y-yeah!
The Protagonist's Story